Good night.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, my God.
It fits.
Good evening.
I'd like to invite you to join us today.
Thank you very much.
I wish I could have done it.
No, no, no, this is from everyone.
I was wondering what you had here.
Then I realized it was a steamed bun.
I finished my makeup.
No makeup.
Rounded skin eyes
Thank you very much for your time today.
Bon appétit.
It's kind of really hot.
It's kind of hot.
It's so hot.
I'm sweating on my own.
I can feel the heat just by being here.
It's really hot right now.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
It tastes so good!
I'm starving.
Please eat.
Oh, it's good. It's a big serving.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Who brought this cute girl?
All right, let's have a cup of ramen.
I got a cup of ramen and some miso soup.
This is harder than normal.
Nothing's right.
We'll have strawberries or chocolate later for dessert.
What do you want now? I'm going to check the song.
Or should I be patient?
What kind of shark's fin is that?
As if to check.
I thought you might have one.
It's Yokohama today.
Hmm.
You like Yokohama too much, Tokise?
Then let's all go to Kanagawa.
Let's absorb it.
To Kanagawa
I'm one of Oharu's friends.
I had seafood this morning.
So delicious!
Good morning.
Good morning, please.
OK.
I just took this picture and I'm starving.
Get up, a little early.
Today,
It's the springtime world of the crush spring.
It's Landy's.
What a coincidence,
The rock full outfit is black, but this last period has a cute outfit in black too.
Perfect timing.
Gohan!
Cute.
They'll be splashing it all over the fridge.
Oh, that's it! The fridge.
Yay.
Jerry's.
Normally I would have chosen orange, but today I'll have grapes.
I'm going to eat it.
One day.
When I wake up in the morning, I wake up.
So, I played with my cell phone for a while,
Then my sister woke me up,
She massaged my feet as soon as I woke up,
From my feet to my back.
It was super nice.
So my feet are a little more moist than usual.
My feet.
Then, I had katsudon (pork cutlet served on top of a bowl of rice) in the morning,
I'm going to a concert today.
I ate katsudon and put honey in my balance juice,
I drank it.
Thanks for the food.
Say hi later.
Bye bye.
This is soup, right?
This place is amazing!
This is not it.
My grandson's yolk splitting.
It's true.
Now
With the help of Mr. Furusawa
I'm going to run.
About now.
I'm going to break my arm.
Oh, no.
One of them broke his arm.
Yes, in the middle.
It's so sudden. It's so sudden.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
It fits!
Asa-chan!
What's the matter?
The other day
Furusawa-san's recording
The cutest thing I've ever seen.
of the cutest thing
I was able to be there.
at the recording session
I was going to buy a fan
I wanted to buy one, but they were sold out
I heard that they were sold out
I heard that
Mr. Tokise gave me a set of
Ms. Tokise brought a set of Nichiwa goods
in Ms. Furusawa's room.
Ms. Furusawa's room.
Thank you for your hard work!
Isn't it amazing?
He was holding a penlight.
I'm so glad!
Thank you for watching!
The eyeliner on the bar bag gives it a really nice touch.
It's different from the usual.
What's different?
The makeup.
Different?
It's a little pink.
It's definitely pink.
Good morning. Good morning.
You're rehearsing in 10 minutes?
We're rehearsing in 10 minutes.
Take your pictures, get dressed, and then we'll go to rehearsal.
Okay.
I just said that.
Me, too.
I'm not...
It's too much.
Please.
Please, please, please, please.
I haven't seen it yet.
Wow, that's great.
Thank you very much.
Please.
Please, please, please.
The next hake is in the center?
Below center.
The bottom brush would be in front of this panel, so...
Uh...
I'll just... I'll just...
You can push it with your head.
Yes, sir.
Here?
That's great! It's so big!
Oh, my God! The tiles are black and white!
It's a lot lower than my head.
Oh, watch out!
My head is just off the white line, too.
It's okay! I didn't catch it!
I'll hit it here!
I'll hit it this way!
Good job, guys!
That's great!
He's so cute.
He's so cute. He's so cute.
You're so big!
I can't get down here.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please.
Oh, come on, please.
Please. Kimeki party.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning.
What's up?
You're so cute.
Oh, my God.
I'll be right up there.
He's so cute.
Oh, it's so cute.
Amazing.
It's like a little bit of a love triangle, isn't it?
I don't know. Is it pretty? Is it light?
It's so big!
It's so cute.
I want to take it home.
You're gonna put it in the house?
It won't fit.
It's just too big.
It's a very exciting advertisement.
It's big enough to put in the house.
Front of the house
The nameplate nameplate
So cute!
Raise the stage
Open
It's the same because I'm fixing my hair ornaments
Thank you for your hard work.
I want to go through at about
We're out of here today. Gate 1.
New version
Good ooo
ni
Go him on the outside of the opposite side too.
4 min 20 sec
Finished
What's with the renewal? Fabry.
I heard it's a rock version.
Rock version.
Okay, let's move.
There you go. There you go. There you go.
Found it.
I'm thinking about changing my hair.
What do you think? Gentlemen.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
I like you too much. I like you.
I don't know why.
Wait for the music.
Promise me.
Me from always living
No, no, no, no, no, no.
OK!
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
I'm a turtle.
Turtles.
I can't believe you came for just one song.
Kanami.
Kanami, that's the song Kurosawa-san sang!
Yester.
Oh no, oh no!
Oh no, oh no...
But you can't sing it.
It's not good.
I'm sweating.
Of course you are.
If you said you sang...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
First shot.
That's right, Kanami.
Those big eyes are twice the size of your face.
About the size of your face.
It's yesterdays...
I kinda like it.
You're here for the show.
Talking to you live.
It's really powerful.
Yes, it is.
In the summer.
She likes you.
And he's in the background. Isn't he cute? It's so cute.
It's not like they're always together.
The way he plays, it's so sensual, so loose and flowing.
It's really nice.
I'm sure there's someone crying somewhere.
Just a little bit of my heart
I want to share it with you
I don't know what's in front of me yet
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future
And lead us on the way...
Thank you for watching.
I'll do it now.
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye Good bye To the me of yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
I'll get used to it, it's going to be fine, puddles of sound
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, Good bye, to me of yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a feather, let my tears dry
I'll wear a rainbow dress
La la la la...